(vengeful music begins)
♪ Right now, he's probably slow dancing ♪
♪ With a bleach-blonde tramp ♪
♪ And she's probably getting frisky ♪
♪ Right now, he's probably buying her ♪
♪ Some fruity little drink ♪
♪ 'Cause she can't shoot whiskey ♪
♪ Right now, he's probably up
behind her with a pool-stick ♪
♪ Showing her how to shoot a combo ♪
♪ And he don't know ♪
♪ I dug my key into the side ♪
♪ Of his pretty little
souped up four-wheel drive ♪
♪ Carved my name into his leather seats ♪
♪ I took a Louisville
slugger to both headlights ♪
♪ Slashed a hole in all four tires ♪
♪ Maybe next time, he'll
think before he cheats ♪
♪ Right now, she's probably up singing ♪
♪ Some white-trash version
of Shania karaoke ♪
♪ Right now, she's probably
saying, "I'm drunk" ♪
♪ And he's a-thinking that
he's gonna get lucky ♪
♪ Right now, he's probably dabbing on ♪
♪ Three dollars worth
of that bathroom Polo ♪
♪ Oh, and he don't know ♪
♪ Oh, that I dug my key into the side ♪
♪ Of his pretty little
souped four-wheel drive ♪
♪ Carved my name into his leather seats ♪
♪ I took a Louisville
slugger to both headlights ♪
♪ Slashed a hole in all four tires ♪
♪ Maybe next time, he'll
think before he cheats ♪
♪ I might've saved a little
trouble for the next girl ♪
♪ A-'cause the next time that he cheats ♪
♪ Oh, you know it won't be on me ♪
(vengeful music decreases)
♪ No, not on me ♪
(vengeful music swells)
♪ 'Cause I dug my key into the side ♪
♪ Of his pretty little
souped up four-wheel drive ♪
♪ Carved my name into his leather seats ♪
♪ I took a Louisville
slugger to both headlights ♪
♪ Slashed a hole in all four tires ♪
♪ Maybe next time, he'll
think before he cheats ♪
♪ Oh, maybe next time, he'll think ♪
♪ Before he cheats ♪
♪ Oh, before he cheats ♪
♪ Oh ♪